(Penny:)So I hear you and the lost boys
are having a bachelor party tonight.
(Leonard:)Yeah. Just going to a restaurant, get some
steaks, Scotch. Nothing to worry about.
(Penny:)Why should I worry?
(Leonard:)It's a bachelor party. There could be
strippers. Wouldn't that make you jealous?
Uh, come on, Leonard, it's you.
What's gonna happen?
(Penny:)If there was a stripper, all you'd do...
...is avoid eye contact and maybe offer
to help her kid with his homework.
Hey, I'm a young man
in his sexual prime.
(Leonard:)Under the right conditions,
l am capable ofjust really crazy stuff.
(Penny:)Really? What is the craziest thing
you've ever done with a woman?
The time we had sex in the ocean
does not count.
Oh, come on, that's gotta count.
(Leonard:)There was a really strong undertow.
We could've died.
(Penny:)Well, have fun tonight.
(Leonard:)Oh, I will. There is no telling
what might happen.
Yeah, there is, heh.
(Leonard:)You know, there's nothing wrong helping
some woman's kid get through their SATs.